

MOHAMMAD AL-OBALLI

LARAVEL DEVELOPER





+962 779480189



mohammadoballi6@gmail.com



@mohoballi02

₹<u>©</u>}-Skills

php **Object Oriented Programming** html,css, js problem solving bootstrap laravel

java

Relational database design

Oracle 10g

mysql

Education

software engineering

2016 - 2020

Hu uinversity

About Me

Mohamed is a software developer with two years of experience. He worked on more than three projects for a regional company such as kikclans using technology laravel, He has knowledge with databases and the relationships between them, as well as skill in other languages such as C++, Java, and ui-ux using Figma



project

Auto Shop mobile app

kicklanc - Palestine

2022

· Design and development of an online car showroom

mo university portal

kicklanc - Palestine

2022

· Design and development of a university website

scout website

kicklanc - Palestine

2022

· Design and development of a scout website

Work Experience

mostaql.com 2020-now

laravel php

· A Laravel developer is like any other software developer. BUT, one thing that sets them apart is their special affinity for the Laravel framework using the PHP programming language.

Marj-Alhmam scout 2019-now

Media Officer

- Photographer
- Video montage
- · Social media administrator